foxyapp.com 2015-04-26

# 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Introductory Note** :

At VpFun.com , we understand the importance of safeguarding any information that you may provide to us in the course of using our products and services. Furthermore, we appreciate your choice to share certain information with us as it enables us to improve our products and services. We understand our role in safeguarding your data, and take this role seriously. As such, we follow two relentless principles. First, user data collection should be limited to the extent necessary to enable the proper functioning of a given product or service. Second, user data collection, sharing, and use should be transparent.

Our data collection, sharing, and use policies, as set forth below, were crafted in furtherance of the two principles enumerated above. Should you have any questions or concerns about any privacy-related issues, or the subject matter of the Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to get in touch with us at the following Email address: Info@VpFun.com

**I. What does this Privacy Policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy governs your use of the software gaming application, created by VpFun.com, (the "Application"). The Application includes features relating to fictitious racing of automobiles, earning points related thereto, and sharing of game results. This Privacy Policy pertains solely to VpFun.com.

**II. What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?**

A. User Provided Information

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including: 

  * Device Information: We collect device-specific information when you access our Services from a mobile device, including your hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information and country.
  * Use Information: We collect information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, game play activity, interactions with other players, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
  * Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that helps us to improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "Your Choices" below. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels"). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon.
  * Other Information Collected with Permission: Our mobile applications that are distributed through various "app" stores may also request permission to automatically collect other information from your mobile device, including your email address. We may only collect this information with your authorization in accordance with your device operating system's permission process.

B. Automatically Collected Information

In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device's unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application. This information cannot be identified with any individual players, but is collected for the purpose of analyzing, improving, and/or enabling the provision of various game features and functions.

**III. Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?**

We share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may disclose User Provided Information and Automatically Collected Information in accordance with the following:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
  * with our trusted service providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this Privacy Policy;
  * if VpFun.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information;
  * to advertisers and third party advertising networks and analytics companies as described below under the Section entitled Automatic Data Collection and Advertising.

**Information we might obtain from other sources**

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, if you create or log into your account through a social media site, we will have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information, profile picture, phone number, email address, gender, date of birth and friends lists, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such social media site.

**Use Of Information**

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
  * Setup your gWallet account and manage the VpFun.com credits that you earn and use across our Services;
  * Provide and deliver the products and services you request and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices;
  * Send you communications about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by VpFun.com and other companies, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content, suggested connections or features that match user profiles or activities;
  * Process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service;
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.
  * VpFun.com is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

**Sharing of Information**

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;
  * With other users of the in connection with the social features of the Services. For example, your username, profile picture and the virtual content you have accumulated in a game may be visible to other users of that game. Additionally, information that you provide in your account registration for a forum and your forum comments may be available to other forum users.
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Glu or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company;
  * With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.
  * We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**Why do we require certain Permissions in our apps?**

  * (a) android.permission.INTERNET: This permission are required to display ads.
  * (b) android.permission.ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE: See (a)
  * (c) android.permission.ACCESS_WIFI_STATE: See (a)
  * (d) android.permission.WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE: This permission is used in the following cases:   
Some applications have possibility to save a scene of the play. ( with "Save" button ).   
Some applications are loading images ONLY from install directory of app. 
  * (e) android.permission.READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE: See (d)

**IV. Automatic Data Collection and Advertising.**

We work with analytics companies to help us understand how the Application is being used, such as the frequency, nature, and duration of usage.

We work with advertisers and third party advertising networks, who need to know how you interact with advertising provided in the Application, which helps us keep the Application free to download. Advertisers and advertising networks may use some of the information collected by the Application. To protect the anonymity of this information, we use encryption technology to help ensure that these third parties can't identify you personally.

These third parties may also obtain anonymous information about other applications you've downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit, your non-precise location information (e.g., your zip code), and other non-precise location information in order to help analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Application and elsewhere. We may also share encrypted versions of information you have provided in order to enable our partners to append other available information about you for analysis or advertising related use.

As of the date of this Privacy Policy, we share your mobile device's unique ID with the following entities: AdMob. Although we take care to ensure that we work only with trustworthy and reputable advertising and analytics companies, we encourage users of the Application to read and understand the privacy policies of the entities identified above. These privacy policies may be viewed at the following:

AdMob: www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy

**V. Phone Features.**

In order to provide you with the best gaming experience, the Application may require access to certain features of your mobile device, such as the touchscreen, speakers, vibration mechanism, and features related to network connectivity.

The Application does not access to your mobile device's address book, text messages, pictures, documents, or any other features not explicitly identified within this Privacy Policy.

**VI. Frictionless Sharing.**

The Application allows you to share certain information with your Facebook account. Prior to doing so, we encourage users to read Facebook's privacy policy in order to understand how your information may be used by Facebook. Facebook's Data Use Policy may be found here:

http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/

**VII. What are my opt-out rights?**

You may opt-out of, and stop, all information collection by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.

**VIII. Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information.**

We will retain User Provided Information for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time after. We do our best to ensure that any User Provided Information is safely discarded as soon as practicable after you uninstall the Application. We may retain Automatically Collected information for up to 12 months and thereafter may store it in aggregate. If you'd like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at Info@VpFun.com and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly.

**IX. Children.**

We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of thirteen (13). No children under the age of thirteen (13) may use the Application unless such use is with informed parental consent. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has used the Application, or provided us with information, without parental consent, he or she should contact us as soon as possible at Info@VpFun.com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

**X. Security.**

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Furthermore, we encrypt your information whenever needed to prevent unauthorized disclosure. Where certain identifying information is not necessary, we de-identify your information prior to disclosure. Please be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

**XI. Changes.**

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting a new Privacy Policy within the Application and/or on our Web site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

**XII. Your Consent.**

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of User Provided and Automatically Collection information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information.

**XIII. Contact Us.**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at info@VpFun.com.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site.   
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
